trivia_data = [
    {
        "question": "Which hero says “Justice rains from above!” when using their ultimate ability?",
        "answers": ["Pharah", "Mercy", "Reinhardt", "Soldier 76"],
        "correct": 0  # The index of the correct answer in the list
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero is a former professional gamer from South Korea?",
        "answers": ["D.Va", "Mei", "Genji", "Sombra"],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero is the leader of the Deadlock Gang?",
        "answers": ["Cassidy", "Ashe", "Roadhog", "Reaper"],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero is a former member of the Australian Liberation Front?",
        "answers": ["Symmetra", "Zenyatta", "Junkrat", "Bastion"],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero is a former Talon operative who defected to Overwatch?",
        "answers": ["Widowmaker", "Moira", "Genji", "Baptiste"],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero is a former Overwatch agent who was presumed dead after a mission in Venice?",
        "answers": ["Ana", "Reinhardt", "Soldier 76", "Winston"],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero is a hacker who was part of the Los Muertos gang in Mexico?",
        "answers": ["Sombra", "Echo", "Ashe", "Hanzo"],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero is a former Overwatch agent who was the leader of Blackwatch?",
        "answers": ["Moira", "Genji", "Reaper", "Tracer"],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero was the test pilot of the Slipstream project?",
        "answers": ["Pharah", "Mercy", "Winston", "Tracer"],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero was the mentor of Genji?",
        "answers": ["Hanzo", "Zenyatta", "Reinhardt", "Lifeweaver"],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero is the daughter of Torbjörn?",
        "answers": ["Bastion", "Mei", "Brigitte", "Echo"],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero has the highest base health pool?",
        "answers": ["Reinhardt", "Roadhog", "Wrecking Ball", "D.Va"],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero has the shortest ultimate charge time?",
        "answers": ["Tracer", "Zarya", "Genji", "Junkrat"],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero is the leader of Junkertown and a former mech fighter?",
        "answers": ["Junker Queen", "Junkrat", "Roadhog", "Reaper"],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero is a ruthless leader of Talon who believes that conflict is the only way to strengthen humanity?",
        "answers": ["Genji", "Moira", "Doomfist", "Sombra"],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero is a new model of OR15 defense robot?",
        "answers": ["Reinhardt", "Echo", "Bastion", "Orisa"],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero is an advanced robot created by Dr. Mina Liao?",
        "answers": ["Torbjörn", "Echo", "Orisa", "Lifeweaver"],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero is a freedom fighter who stole Vishkar’s sonic technology?",
        "answers": ["Torbjörn", "Symmetra", "Lucio", "Mei"],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero is a shrine maiden and a protector of Kanezaka?",
        "answers": ["Kiriko", "Genji", "Tracer", "Hanzo"],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero was fascinated by the potential of hard-light to manipulate life forms and create new ones?",
        "answers": ["Symmetra", "Ana", "Moira", "Lifeweaver"],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero is a bounty hunter who was caught by Overwatch during a sting operation and given a choice to join them or rot in prison?",
        "answers": ["Hanzo", "Cassidy", "Ashe", "Ramattra"],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero is a brilliant astrophysicist who was exposed to a black hole experiment that gave him the ability to manipulate gravity?",
        "answers": ["Winston", "Reaper", "Sigma", "Mercy"],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero is a scientist who was raised on the moon and joined Overwatch?",
        "answers": ["Winston", "Wrecking Ball", "Mercy", "Moira"],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero is a climatologist and an adventurer who uses her endothermic blaster and weather drones to study and preserve the environment?",
        "answers": ["Kiriko", "Ramattra", "Mei", "Lucio"],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero is a Canadian soldier and an Overwatch agent who leads the team in Overwatch 2",
        "answers": ["Soldier 76", "Reaper", "Mercy", "Sojourn"],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero is an engineer and an inventor who helped design many weapons for Overwatch?",
        "answers": ["Ana", "Torbjörn", "Winston", "Echo"],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero was the head of medical research for Overwatch?",
        "answers": ["Moira", "Mercy", "Lifeweaver", "Kiriko"],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero is the heir of the Shimada clan but who left his family after killing his brother?",
        "answers": ["Reaper", "Genji", "Sombra", "Hanzo"],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero is a crusader who fights with honor and courage?",
        "answers": ["Zarya", "Pharah", "Reinhardt", "Brigitte"],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero was student and brother to Zenyatta?",
        "answers": ["Ramattra", "Echo", "Hanzo", "Tracer"],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero is a Russian soldier and a weightlifting champion?",
        "answers": ["Reinhardt", "Zarya", "Baptiste", "Soldier 24"],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero escaped from the lunar colony with Winston and built a combat mech from junk parts?",
        "answers": ["Roadhog", "Sigma", "D.Va", "Wrecking Ball"],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero is a combat omnic who developed a curious personality and a fondness for nature?",
        "answers": ["Echo", "Torbjörn", "Bastion", "Orisa"],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero was saved by Overwatch and trained by Zenyatta to find peace with himself?",
        "answers": ["Ramattra", "Genji", "Reaper", "Widowmaker"],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero is a vigilante and a former leader of Overwatch who was presumed dead after an explosion at the headquarters?",
        "answers": ["Soldier 76", "Ana", "Winston", "Sojourn"],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero is an architect and an agent of Vishkar Corporation?",
        "answers": ["Ana", "Dr. Mina Liao", "Maximillian", "Symmetra"],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero was brainwashed and turned into a cold-blooded killer by Talon?",
        "answers": ["Moira", "Reaper", "Widowmaker", "Sigma"],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which hero is a geneticist and a member of Talon who seeks to unlock the secrets of life?",
        "answers": ["Mercy", "Moira", "Lifeweaver", "Doomfist"],
        "correct": 1
    }
]
